<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>resources - Tag - Morris&#39; Blogs</title>
        <link>http://example.org/tags/resources/</link>
        <description>resources - Tag - Morris&#39; Blogs</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><managingEditor>morrishohoho@gmail.com (Morris)</managingEditor>
            <webMaster>morrishohoho@gmail.com (Morris)</webMaster><lastBuildDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 11:04:49 &#43;0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://example.org/tags/resources/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
    <title>Courses Resources</title>
    <link>http://example.org/posts/resources/resource_courses/</link>
    <pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 11:04:49 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Morris</author>
    <guid>http://example.org/posts/resources/resource_courses/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Course Map CSDIY Courses Wireless IoT Introduction, Prof.Jiliang Wang: IoT techenique introduction that explains wireless communication and sensing. (In Chinese) Embeded Systems Bootlin-Embeded Linux CTF MetaCTF_Blog: Basic concepts introduction of CTF, hosted by UVA undergraduate students. Tools Tutorials Vim Interactive Vim tutorial: A guide to basic vim commands. Vim9.0 Quick Setup Tutorial: A qucik setup tutorial of VIM 9.0 Setup, including how to install plugins. ]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Misc Resources</title>
    <link>http://example.org/posts/resources/resource_misc/</link>
    <pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 11:04:49 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Morris</author>
    <guid>http://example.org/posts/resources/resource_misc/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[About Here are some useful resources. In SCU SCU网络避坑指北 SCU计金作业汇总 Interesting Tools Code Visualizer: A very useful tool to visualize the code execution process, like the stack and the heap. It is used in UCB CS61A and 61B. Interesting Websites Trolley Problems: A interactive website with trolley problems.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Music Resources</title>
    <link>http://example.org/posts/resources/resource_music/</link>
    <pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 11:04:49 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Morris</author>
    <guid>http://example.org/posts/resources/resource_music/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Music Resources electroSmash: Circuit introduction of famous guitar effects unit. JazzStandards : Well-known Jazz standards lists. MusicMap : The Genealogy and History of Popular Music Genres. Encyclopaedia Metallum: The famous metal archives. ]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Reading Resources</title>
    <link>http://example.org/posts/resources/resource_reading/</link>
    <pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 11:04:49 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Morris</author>
    <guid>http://example.org/posts/resources/resource_reading/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Undergradute Methodology 交大生存手册 Methodology How to read Paper: There is a well-known essay that recommends a three-step process for reading a paper. How to Look for Ideas in Computer Science Research: Written by Prof. Zhiyun Qian. The idea of finding vulnerabilities is impressive. GoodReading: A senior SCUer recommended reading resources. Dingzeyu Li Podcast: This is a podcast channel. The topics are mainly about the personal]]></description>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
